http://www.alpharhochi.org/policies

Policies
Privacy Policy
Alpha Rho Chi Fraternity respects the privacy of its members and visitors to our website. Our websites are not set up to track, collect, or distribute personal information not entered by visitors.
Alpha Rho Chi does not share or sell member information, such as names and addresses, to vendors for bulk mail solicitations. Alpha Rho Chi does not sell email addresses, telephone numbers, or demographic information. Membership information is shared with the fraternity’s chapters, alumni associations, and the Alpha Rho Chi Foundation for fraternal purposes.
Nonmember information obtained through registration or order forms is used for internal APX purposes and to fulfill the request; Alpha Rho Chi does not share or sell this information to vendors for bulk mail solicitations.
All financial data is encrypted by Authorize.net for the sole purpose of payment processing and no financial information is stored by Alpha Rho Chi Fraternity.
External Websites
Please note that alpharhochi.org contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites, and encourage our users to be aware when leaving our site that they read the privacy statements of each website that might collect personally identifying information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by alpharhochi.org.
Returns Policy
All sales through alpharhochi.org are final unless otherwise noted. Purchases listed as eligible for return/refund must first be approved, based on the terms set forth on the order page, by the Worthy Grand Estimator and the fraternity contact listed on the sales receipt.  Please provide your name, contact information, sales receipt and reason for requesting a credit or exchange with the request.
Contact: Worthy Grand Estimator (WGE)
Email: wge@alpharhochi.org
Phone: 774-290-4480
